Standard, William Papers 5258
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- General NMU. Washington Newsletter, Issued by the CIO Maritime Committee, 1944-1945 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  November 1944 - March 1945
- General NMU. Washington Newsletter, Issued by the CIO Maritime Committee, 1945-1946 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  August 1945 - December 1946
- General NMU. Washington Newsletter, Issued by the CIO Maritime Committee, 1945 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  March 1945 - July 1945
- General NMU. Washington Newsletter, Issued by the CIO Maritime Committee, 1944 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  June 1944 - November 1944
- General NMU. Washington Newsletter, Issued by the CIO Maritime Committee, 1944 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  March 1944 - June 1944
- General NMU. Washington Newsletter, Issued by the CIO Maritime Committee, 1943-1944 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  October 1943 - March 1944
- General NMU. Women's Auxiliary, 1943-1945 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  Includes newspaper clipping, constitution, and tax exemption certificate.
- General NMU. Workmen's Compensation, 1944 (Box 8, Folder 30)
- General NMU. Worthen, Eugene v. Joseph Curran, 1943-1947 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  Includes motions, depositions, memorandum and a report of charges. Member expelled from NMU
- General NMU. Worthen, Eugene v. Joseph Curran, 1943-1947 (Box 8, Folder 32)
- General NMU. Worthen, Eugene v. Joseph Curran, 1943-1947 (Box 8, Folder 33)
- General NMU. NMU Regular Membership Meeting, 1943 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  February 11, 1943
- General files. Publications, 1939-1947 (Box 8, Folder 35)
- General files. Railway Labor Act, amendments to. (Box 8, Folder 36)
- General NMU. Agreements, 1939-1947 (Box 8, Folder 37)
- General NMU. Inflation Law re Collective Bargaining (Box 8, Folder 38)
- General NMU. Pamphlets, 1939-1947 (Box 8, Folder 39)
- Scrapbooks, 1934-1947 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  Two scrap books of newspaper clippings.
- NWLB. NMU adv. Army Transport Service. Exhibits., 1943-1944 (Box 10, Folder 1)